{
    "subject": "resource/Truckin'_Magazine",
    "predicate": "property/circulationYear",
    "object": "2011",
    "human_readable": "The circulation year of Truckin' Magazine was 2011.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8191250562667847,
            "question": "What year marked the beginning of Truckin' Magazine's circulation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7552952170372009,
            "question": "In what year did Truckin' Magazine begin its publication?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7496033310890198,
            "question": "What year was Truckin' Magazine first circulated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7383806109428406,
            "question": "The first edition of Truckin' Magazine circulated in which year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7154518365859985,
            "question": "What year established Truckin' Magazine as a publication?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6565062403678894,
            "question": "Truckin' Magazine commenced its journey in what year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6158763766288757,
            "question": "When did Truckin' Magazine make its appearance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5479789972305298,
            "question": "Truckin' Magazine's debut year was?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.52863609790802,
            "question": "When was the inaugural issue of Truckin' Magazine released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4953118860721588,
            "question": "During which year did Truckin' Magazine first reach readers?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The circulation year of Truckin' Magazine was 2011.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1989_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the inaugural issue of Truckin' Magazine released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1989_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Truckin' Magazine's debut year was?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1989_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Truckin' Magazine make its appearance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1989_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1989_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1989_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1989_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1989_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1989_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1989_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1989_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1989_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1989_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1989_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided does not mention any details about the circulation year of Truckin' Magazine or similar information that could confirm or deny the statement regarding its circulation year being 2011."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}